A Guide to the W. W. LaPrade and Brothers Records, 1803-2001 (bulk 1900-1970)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Richmond City Vertical files, ca. 1920-1990 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 31-43)
  - Richmond R-3. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Federal Reserve Bank
  - Richmond S. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Richmond S. (Box 39, Folder 17-19)
    First and Merchants Bank
  - Richmond S. (Box 39, Folder 20-22)
    Riverfront Plaza
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 22a)
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 23)
    211 S. 14th street
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 24)
    114-122 Va. street- Hill building
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 25)
    Lady Byrd Co.
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 26)
    Council for America's First Freedom
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 27)
    14th and Main streets
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 28)
    Jackson Warehouse apartments
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 29)
    Old railroad YMCA
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 39, Folder 30)
    1401-1429 E. Cary street
  - Richmond S-1. (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    Shockoe Plaza
  - Richmond T. (Box 40, Folder 3a)
  - Richmond T. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Manchester Board and Paper
  - Richmond T. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Reynolds Metal (South plant)
  - Richmond T. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Richmond T-1. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Richmond T-2. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Richmond T-3. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Richmond T-4. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Richmond U. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Richmond U-1. (Box 40, Folder 11a)
  - Richmond U-2. (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
  - Richmond U-2. (Box 40, Folder 14)
    700 Gordon Ave.
  - Richmond U-3. (Box 40, Folder 14a)
  - Richmond U-3. (Box 40, Folder 14b)
  - Richmond U-3. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    Diesel School (old) property
  - Richmond V. (Box 40, Folder 15a)
  - Richmond V-1. (Box 40, Folder 16-18)
  - Richmond V-1. (Box 40, Folder 19)
    First Baptist Church of South Richmond
  - Richmond V-2. (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Richmond V-3. (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Richmond V-4. (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Richmond V-5. (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Richmond V-6. (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Richmond V-7. (Box 40, Folder 25)
    Waste Management Inc.
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 26-27)
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 28)
    Amoco
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 29)
    Tristate Electrical Supply Co. Inc.
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 30)
    Center Hill
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 31)
    Union Oil
  - Richmond V-8. (Box 40, Folder 32)
    James T. Sloan
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Colonial Ford
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Federal Paper Co.
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Little Oil Co.
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Melrose
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 6-13)
    Old Bowles Quarry (Richmond Quarry), Tidewater
  - Richmond V-9. (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
    Southside Gardens and additional block F
  - Richmond V-9-2. (Box 41, Folder 16-17)
    Southmont Village
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 19)
    E.R. Carpenter Co. Inc.
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 20)
    Deepwater Rd.
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 21)
    James McGraw Inc.
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 22)
    Peck- Iron and Metal (tracing in oversize surveys Big File Rich 2)
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 41, Folder 23)
    Southampton
  - Richmond V-10. (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    Tidewater Quarry (Richmond Quarry), see also Richmond V-9
  - Richmond V-10-2. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Summer Hill Plaza
  - Richmond V-10-B. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Pinehurst and vicinity
  - Richmond V-10-C. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Richmond V-10-C. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Davee Gardens
  - Richmond V-11-A. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Richmond V-11-A. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Richmond V-11-A. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Jefferson Davis Park
  - Richmond V-11-A. (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Pierre Warwick
  - Richmond V-11-B. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Richmond V-11-B. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Farm Fresh
  - Richmond V-11-B. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Jefferson Davis Highway
  - Richmond V-11-B. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Sisco Ave.
  - Richmond V-11-C. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Richmond W. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Richmond W-1. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Richmond W-1. (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Hicks Construction Co. Inc.
  - Richmond W-2. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Richmond X. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Richmond X-1. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Richmond X-2. (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Richmond X-3. (Box 42, Folder 22a)
  - Richmond X-4. (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Richmond X-5. (Box 42, Folder 23a)
  - Richmond X-6. (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Richmond Y. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Richmond Y-1. (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Richmond Y-1. (Box 42, Folder 27)
    Forest Hills Association LP
  - Richmond Y-1. (Box 42, Folder 28)
    Ray Loba
  - Richmond Y-2. (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Richmond Y-3. (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Richmond Y-4. (Box 24, Folder 31-32)
  - Richmond Y-5. (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Richmond Y-6. (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Richmond Y-7. (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Richmond Y-7. (Box 42, Folder 36)
    Sumerset Glen apartments
  - Richmond Y-7. (Box 42, Folder 37)
    Woodside Court
  - Richmond Y-8. (Box 42, Folder 38-39)
    Loch Lomond Realty Co.
  - Richmond Y-8-1. (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Richmond Y-9. (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Richmond Y-10. (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Richmond Z. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Richmond Z-1. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Z-2. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Richmond Z-3. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Richmond Z-A. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Westover Hills Subdivision A
  - Richmond Z-B. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Westover Hills Subdivision B
  - Richmond Z-C. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Westover Hills Subdivision C
  - Richmond Z-D. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    Westover Hills Subdivision D
  - Richmond Z-D. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Richmond Z-E. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    Westover Hills Subdivision E
- Series IV: Other Cities and Counties Vertical files, ca. 1920-1990 (bulk 1940-1970)., Extent: 23 boxes. (Box 44-66)
  This series includes plats and surveys, correspondence and deeds, relating to other cities and counties in Virginia. The more recent files, ca. 1980-1990, also include site plan applications, newspaper clippings, utility, sewer, and topographical maps, memos, soil evaluation reports, and building ordinances relating to the properties.
  Arranged alphabetically by county or city. Within each county/city the files are then arranged alphabetically by property owner or name of property.
  - Albermarle Co. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Gulf Oil Co.
  - Albermarle Co. (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
    Hydraulic Road Apts.
  - Albermarle Co. (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
    Rivanna Water and Sewer Authority
  - Albermarle Co. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Children's Rehabilitation Center
  - Amelia Co. (Box 44, Folder 7-13)
  - Amelia Co. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Notes on Amelia Springs
  - Amelia Co. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    Three States Realty Co. Wastefield Tract, Jackson district
  - Amherst Co. (Box 44, Folder 16-18)
    Sweet Briar College
  - Appomattox Co. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    Spout Spring P.O.
  - Augusta Co. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Augusta Co. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    American Oil, Staunton
  - Brunswick Co. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Bryant Stith topo
  - Brunswick Co. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Lawrenceville
  - Buckingham Co. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 4-6)
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    American Oil Co.
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Camp Parater
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 9-13)
    Catalpa subdivision, Bowling Green
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    Cities Service Oil Co.
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    Gulf Oil Co., Carmel Church
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Gulf Oil Co., Ladysmith
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    Humble Oil co.
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Meadow Farm
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Pinebrook Acres
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 20)
    Richmond City Jail, proposed
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 21-22)
    Shell Oil Co.
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 23)
    Standard Oil Co.
  - Caroline Co. (Box 45, Folder 24)
    Whitecrest
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 1-6)
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 7-12)
    The Forest
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Sandy Point Project
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Tettington Plantation subdivision
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Tidewater Quarries
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
    Izaak Walton
  - Charles City Co. (Box 46, Folder 18-19)
    Westbury Farm
  - Charlotte Co. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Charlottesville (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Barracks Road Shopping Center
  - Chesapeake (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Battlefield Boulevard
  - Chesapeake (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Chesapeake Redevelopment and Housing Authority
  - Chesapeake (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Safeway
  - Colonial Beach (Box 47, Folder 6-8)
    Bluffs Point Court
  - Colonial Beach (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Riverwood Apts.
  - Craig Co. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Culpeper Co. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Cumberland Co. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Danville (Box 47, Folder 13)
    Ballou Park Shopping Center
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 14-17)
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 18)
    Appomattox River, Three State Realty Co.
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Camelot
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 20)
    R.B. Craddock
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 21)
    Crestview Co.
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 22)
    H.W. Harrison
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 23)
    Hazelwood subdivision
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 24)
    Humble Oil Co.
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Stuckey's
  - Dinwiddie Co. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Tarmac, Quarry, Clayton, Marek
  - Dumfries. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    GE VEPCO, Possum Point
  - Elizabeth City Co. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Gwynnfield
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Maryfield
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Richneck Tract near Tappahannock
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    South Hill Banks
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 9-11)
    Ware property
  - Essex Co. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Wilson Acres subdivision and Rappahannock Beach subdivision
  - Fairfax Co. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Gunston Hall and VEPCO
  - Fairfax Co. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Fort Hunt Senior High School
  - Fairfax Co. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    George Mason University Women's softball field
  - Fairfax Co. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Giant Food Co.
  - Farmville. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Fauquier Co. (Box 48, Folder 18)
    Humble Oil
  - Fluvanna Co. and Fork Union (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Fort A.P. Hill. (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Frederick Co. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Farmers/Merchants Bank
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 49, Folder 5-6)
    Mary Washington College
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Ukrops
  - Fredericksburg. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    VEPCO
  - Front Royal. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Humphrey Tourist Camp
  - Gloucester Co. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 12-15)
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    James River Estates
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    Dr. Edmund LaPrade
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 18)
    Richmond Country Club
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    St. Mary's Episcopal Church
  - Goochland Co. (Box 49, Folder 20)
    John Siegel tract
  - Greensville Co. (Box 49, Folder 21-24)
  - Hanover Co. (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    General
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Ashland Hanover Shopping Center
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 6-9)
    Avis Rent-A-Car Co.
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Best Products
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Dr. Hill Carter
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Colonial Estates
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    Country Club Hills
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Country Club Hills Sewer plant
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Kenwood Homes
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Ruby Kiser
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    Mobile Oil Co.
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 18-19)
    Oak Hill Estates
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 20)
    Poplar Springs
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 21)
    Richmond Food Stores Inc.
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Town of Ashland
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 23)
    Blair A. Troutman
  - Hanover Co., Ashland district. (Box 50, Folder 24)
    J.A. Walder
  - Hanover Co., Beaverdam district. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Hanover Co., Beaverdam district. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Stewart D. Jones
  - Hanover Co., Beaverdam district. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    North Woods subdivision
  - Hanover Co., Beaverdam district. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Beechwood Farms
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 7-7a)
    B.P. Oil Co.
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Concrete Pipe and Products Co.
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Expressway Centers Inc.
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Markwood (renamed Ash Creek by developer)
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    William McLamb
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    Douglas and James Rath
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Donald Timberlake
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    A.B. Tyson estate, N.A. Allen and Arthur Allison
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    Ronald Tyson
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    Oscar H. Weber
  - Hanover Co., Chickahominy district. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    F. Richard Wilton
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Battlefield Farms
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Blue Star Estates
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Flannagan's Mill
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Greenway
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 23)
    Hanover Farms
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 24)
    Hanover Land and Development Co.
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 25-25a)
    Hanover Village Shopping Center
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 26)
    Liberty Hall Hills
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 27)
    Mayfield Farms
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 28)
    W.C. Myers
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 29)
    North Malbourne subdivision
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 30)
    Dale Seslar
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 31-34)
    Spring Meadow
  - Hanover Co., Cold Harbor district (formerly Henry district). (Box 51, Folder 35)
    E.C. Woods
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Burnside Farms
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Cherrydale
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    John G. Duggan
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Hanover Heights South
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Meadowgate
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Robin Ridge
  - Hanover Co., Mechanicsville district. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    Tinsley property
  - Hanover Co., South Anna district. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    Contel Cellular
  - Hanover Co., South Anna district. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    Cooper property
  - Hanover Co., South Anna district. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    J.E. Liesfeld, III
  - Hanover Co., Unknown district. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    Fairgrounds District Center
  - Hanover Co., Unknown district. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    Patrick Henry High School
  - Hanover Co., Unknown district. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Harrisonburg. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Harrisonburg. (Box 53, Folder 2-4)
    James Madison University
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 5-6)
  - Hopewell, Prince George Co., and City Point. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    A- Village; Bailey's Creek; Barrow Tract (auction advertisement); Robert Batte estate; Battleground Annex and Division; Belmont; Buren Gardens; Buren Heights
  - Hopewell, Prince George Co., and City Point. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    Cedar Level (estate of Samuel V. Watkins includes color drawing 1875); W.B. Davie; Eppes estate; Leemont
  - Hopewell, Prince George Co., and City Point. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    Gulf Refining Co.; R.E. Pitchford; John Spencer; Spring Garden Farms; Woodlawn; John Zebeede
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    Annexation 1949, 1951
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    VEPCO Maps of the City of Hopewell
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    Allied Chemical
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    Appomattox Heights; Battleground Annex
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 14-17)
    The Bluffs
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 18)
    Bridgestone and Firestone
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 19)
    Eppes Property
  - Hopewell. (Box 53, Folder 20)
    Hopewell High School
  - James City Co. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - James City Co. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Emergency Operation Center
  - James City Co. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    John Henley tract
  - James City Co. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Mid County Park
  - King and Queen Co. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - King and Queen Co. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Edwin Cox
  - King and Queen and King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 7-10)
  - King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
  - King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    Robert M. Johann
  - King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    J. Harvie Martin Jr. tract
  - King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 15-16)
    Lewis N. Miller Jr. farm
  - King William Co. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    Third Union Baptist Church
  - Lancaster Co. (Box 54, Folder 18-19)
  - Lancaster Co. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    Whitestone (Va.)
  - Langley Air Force Base. (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Loudoun Co. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Louisa Co. (Box 55, Folder 4-7)
    County Office building
  - Louisa Co. (Box 55, Folder 8-9)
    Longway Drive
  - Louisa Co. (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    Louisa Court House
  - Louisa Co. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    VDOT
  - Louisa Co. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    Willow Oaks Restaurant
  - Lunenburg Co. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Lynchburg. (Box 55, Folder 15-16)
  - Madison Co. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Manassas. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Shell Oil
  - Mathews Co. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Mathews Co. (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
    Narrows Marina, Gwynn's Island
  - Mecklenburg Co. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Middlesex Co. (Box 56, Folder 7-8)
  - Middlesex Co. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    Deltaville
  - Montgomery Co. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    VPI
  - New Kent Co. (Box 56, Folder 11-14)
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Brickshire
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Brookwood, water plan
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
    E.F. Crump
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 10-11)
    Five Lakes
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    Holly Fork, control level
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
    Johnston Properties
  - New Kent Co. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    Kenwood Farms
  - Newport News. (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Central Fidelity Bank
  - Newport News. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Charles Apt.
  - Newport News. (Box 58, Folder 3)
    James Landing dam
  - Newport News. (Box 58, Folder 412)
    Oakwood Farms
  - Newport News. (Box 58, Folder 13-14)
    Sinnott motel complex
  - Norfolk. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Norton (and vicinity). (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Northumberland Co. (Box 58, Folder 17-18)
  - Northumberland Co. (Box 58, Folder 19)
    Locksley Hall
  - Nottoway Co. (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Nottoway Co. (Box 58, Folder 21)
    Mannboro Farms
  - Orange (town). (Box 58, Folder 22)
    Bellevue House
  - Orange Co. (Box 58, Folder 23)
    Atlantic Research Co.
  - Orange Co. (Box 58, Folder 24)
    Standard Oil Co. of NJ
  - Petersburg. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Petersburg. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Dunedin and Carrol Arms Apts.
  - Petersburg. (Box 59, Folder 3-4)
    Mt. Olivet Baptist Church
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 5-17)
    N. Huguenot district
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 18)
    N. Huguenot district, Dickenson property
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 19)
    N. Huguenot district, Huguenot Society of the Founders of Manakin
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 20)
    N. Huguenot district, Huguenot Springs
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 21)
    N. Huguenot district, Mrs. Linwood Nunnally
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 22)
    N. Huguenot district, Tomlinson property
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 59, Folder 23-26)
    S. Huguenot district
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    High school
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 60, Folder 3-4)
    Macon district
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 60, Folder 5-10)
    Spencer district
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Schools
  - Powhatan Co. (Box 60, Folder 11a-c)
    Includes 19th century plats and surveys: Huguenot, Scott, and other districts.
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 13-14)
    Berkley Manor
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Bland Ridge
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    Cavalier Farms
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    Humble Oil, Warfield
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Fort Powhatan
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    King subdivision (George Woods estate)
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    Oakhurst subdivision
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    Puddledock Quarry
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Ross Miller School
  - Prince George Co. (Box 60, Folder 24)
    South Plains subdivision
  - Prince William Co. (Box 60, Folder 25)
    Richmond-Washington Highway
  - Quantico. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    FBI Academy, Camp Barrett
  - Richmond Co. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Richmond Co. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Haynesville Dept. of Corrections
  - Roanoke. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Rockbridge Co. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Lexington, Washington and Lee University
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Towns and surrounding area
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 61, Folder 7-8)
    SCS Dams, Notes applicable to all dams
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 61, Folder 9-12)
    SCS Dam 31-A, Rawley Springs
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 61, Folder 13-14)
    SCS Dam 31-A, Rawley Springs, Design report
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 61, Folder 15)
    SCS Dam 31-A, Rawley Springs, Geology report
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    SCS Dam 83, Hones Quarry, Design report
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    SCS Dam 83, Hones Quarry
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 62, Folder 4-8)
    SCS Dam 101, Luray
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Journal of the Geotechnical Engineering Division
  - Rockingham Co. (Box 62, Folder 10)